You lost, friend?
你迷路了吗   朋友
Forgive me for staring.
原谅我的盯视
I don't see many Clippers where I am from.
但在我家乡那边我很少能见到快船人
And I don't see many Rocket men in the city of Angels.
在天使之城我也很少见到火箭人呐
We don't like to smog.
我们不喜欢制造烟雾弹
Come with me, my Beard.
跟我走吧   胡子大人
Now why are you wasting a center like this on a bush-faced choker?
你们为什么要在一个满脸大胡子的人身上浪费一个如此这般好的中锋
Ha ha ha...
哈哈哈
Do you know why the whole world hates a Clipper?
你知道为什么全世界都不喜欢快船人吗
You think you're complaining and you're acting tough makes you worth 2 billion golds?
你认为你在抱怨   你表现得很强硬  会使得你们值得上20亿美金吗
But you're just a whiny little baby
但其实你就是一个爱发牢骚的小屁孩
who's far too slow on the flop.
假摔的时候不知道慢了多少拍